http://www.nepatriotsdraft.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting NE Patriots Draft.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We may collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit
our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Mozilla
Firefox, Internet Explorer) , your I.P. Address, and the address of the
website you were referred from.
We may also request that you participate occasionally in an anonymous
survey, requesting just your sex, age, household income, and other
information which is used to put together demographics for our
advertisers. The survey will not be able to personally identify you, and
simply helps us work with advertisers to design a campaign that will
fit the needs of those who visit this site.
There may be other occasions where you can submit information about
other people. For example, you might submit a friend’s name and e-mail
address to send a story, or invite them to our site. We collect this
information but only in the event we need to step in to prevent abuse or
other misuse of that e-mail tool (e.g. someone e-mailing that story 300
times to one person).
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION
The non-personal information we collect is used to monitor traffic
and also allows us to improve our site to better fit the needs of the
fans who use it.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS
Some of our pages will contain links to products to affiliate sites,
or direct links to the site itself, and their information practices may
be different than ours. By virtue of these relationships, the third
parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors
voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. Visitors should
consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over the
information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
Google, as a third party vendor and one of our advertising mediums,
uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie
enables it to serve ads based on your visit here to and other sites on
the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by
visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use
third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our
website. These companies may use information (not including your name,
address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this
and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services of interest to you. If you would like more information about
this practice and to know your choices about not having this information
used by these companies, click here.
LEGAL NOTES
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to
legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena.
We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement
agency’s request.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against
unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that
personally identifiable information that we collect will never be
disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Comments are closed.
*/ ?>
Recent Posts
Early, Top 100 NCAAF Players Going Into The 2018-19 Season
Why we should be excited about Derek Rivers & 4 Teams That Could Surpass Expectations In 2018
The Patriots 5 Biggest Threats To Another Superbowl Appearence.
Categories NFL (609)
NFL Draft (2,311)
Patriots (1,371)
Scouting Reports (422)
Search NEPD Archives
Click Here To Search
Archives
Select Month
June 2018  (2)
May 2018  (15)
April 2018  (36)
March 2018  (31)
February 2018  (11)
January 2018  (4)
December 2017  (2)
November 2017  (1)
October 2017  (3)
September 2017  (3)
August 2017  (6)
July 2017  (5)
June 2017  (2)
May 2017  (6)
April 2017  (17)
March 2017  (11)
February 2017  (11)
January 2017  (3)
November 2016  (1)
October 2016  (4)
September 2016  (6)
August 2016  (4)
July 2016  (3)
June 2016  (1)
May 2016  (9)
April 2016  (13)
March 2016  (9)
February 2016  (11)
January 2016  (8)
December 2015  (3)
November 2015  (4)
October 2015  (7)
September 2015  (8)
August 2015  (9)
July 2015  (3)
June 2015  (3)
May 2015  (21)
April 2015  (25)
March 2015  (13)
February 2015  (12)
January 2015  (19)
December 2014  (12)
November 2014  (15)
October 2014  (28)
September 2014  (28)
August 2014  (22)
July 2014  (25)
June 2014  (7)
May 2014  (37)
April 2014  (15)
March 2014  (15)
February 2014  (20)
January 2014  (22)
December 2013  (23)
November 2013  (25)
October 2013  (30)
September 2013  (30)
August 2013  (37)
July 2013  (29)
June 2013  (17)
May 2013  (26)
April 2013  (90)
March 2013  (73)
February 2013  (79)
January 2013  (74)
December 2012  (65)
November 2012  (30)
October 2012  (48)
September 2012  (63)
August 2012  (98)
July 2012  (65)
June 2012  (23)
May 2012  (23)
April 2012  (80)
March 2012  (69)
February 2012  (61)
January 2012  (87)
December 2011  (52)
November 2011  (44)
October 2011  (53)
September 2011  (69)
August 2011  (42)
July 2011  (23)
June 2011  (1)
May 2011  (6)
April 2011  (63)
March 2011  (40)
February 2011  (15)
January 2011  (18)
December 2010  (18)
November 2010  (16)
October 2010  (27)
September 2010  (33)
August 2010  (33)
July 2010  (66)
June 2010  (124)
May 2010  (74)
April 2010  (74)
March 2010  (46)
February 2010  (46)
January 2010  (47)
December 2009  (54)
November 2009  (20)
October 2009  (29)
September 2009  (32)
August 2009  (17)
July 2009  (12)
June 2009  (15)
May 2009  (18)
April 2009  (41)
March 2009  (15)
February 2009  (14)
January 2009  (9)
December 2008  (20)
November 2008  (30)
October 2008  (38)
September 2008  (34)
August 2008  (31)
July 2008  (17)
June 2008  (22)
May 2008  (26)
April 2008  (34)
March 2008  (29)
June 201  (1)
Copyright 2012 - NE Patriots Draft - Partner of USA TODAY Sports Digital Properties - Privacy Policy
